♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[in English] Are you sure
we are in the right place?
[security officer, in English] Our intel
told us that the decoder of this town
is the mayor's niece.
[Samir, in English] The man who broke
into the ambassador's office.
[in English] He might be here too.
[in English] Take a good look at him.
[Cita] You shouldn't be
coming here anymore.
Didn't Atoy forbid you?
I'll go ahead.
Well, the watch was exposed
as fake right away.
I hadn't even left yet.
The money was inside the bag. I left it.
[Emerson] You're the woman earlier
at the mall parking lot.
[Ame] What are you saying?
Maybe she just looks like the woman.
- She is Ibyang's mother!
- Huh?
[Audrey] Do you know the man
who tried to take my child?
[Red] Why would I know him?
I'm not a child trafficker.
[Audrey] Are you sure?
[Ibyang] You're a liar!
It's impossible you're my mother.
You're a scammer!
What do you want me to do
so you'll believe me, Ibyang?
- I used to be a scammer too.
- Hmm?
[in Visayan] I was hoping to invite you
to watch a performance outside.
[in Visayan] I'm scared
someone might see me.
[in Visayan] I know you're afraid
of being seen by the ambassador.
[in Visayan] But let me tell you,
you're safe here.
[Lily, in Visayan]
I know, but can I stay here?
I feel safer here.
[dagger swishes]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
[in Visayan] Our guest will be happy
when they watch you.
[woman, in Visayan]
You can see it clearly.
[in Visayan] Do better
on your performance at the fiesta.
[in Visayna] You can count on us, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- [in Visayan] Thank you, Mayor.
[ominous music playing]
[secretary, in English] Oh.
Picture, Mayor.
[chuckles softly]
[man] Stop!
- [screaming and panicking]
- [foreboding music playing]
Son of a thread.
[guard] Cover the Mayor!
Cover him! Cover the Mayor!
We're escaping!
[clamoring]
[Mercado on the device] Lily Santiago,
the head of IT of the embassy.
[tense music playing]
- Come.
- God-- Let go of me.
- Godfather, help! Godfather, he…
- [hushes]
- Shut! Shut up.
- [whimpering]
[mutters]
I won't hurt you.
Why should I believe you?
Because I'm not the one firing shots.
The embassy people are there.
They want to take you.
- Come.
- [gasps]
[guard] Cover the Mayor!
We're escaping!
Hurry!
[music swells]
[music fades]
[rousing music playing]
[in English] Go.
[in English] Good evening, Mr. Mayor.
[in English] Where is she?
- [music swells]
- [soft sobs]
[music fades]
[armed man] Where are you going?!
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[woman sobs softly]
[in English] I don't want to play games.
[groans]
[in English] I will ask you one more time.
[in English] Where is she?
- [music fades]
- [woman sobs softly]
- [grunts and groans]
- [thumps]
- [gunshot]
- [grunting]
[groans]
[grunting]
[action music playing]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[sobs]
[in English] Maybe I'll ask your wife.
[in English] Maybe she's smarter than you.
[sobs]
[suspicious music playing]
- [in English] Where is the girl?
- [sobs]
[in Visayan] Don't say anything!
Don't say anything!
[wailing]
[in English] Where is she?!
[wails, in English] Last room on the left.
[in English] Please, let go
of my husband! [wails]
[in English] Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
[wails]
[Samir, in English] Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[wails]
[music fades]
[in English] This is bad.
Dad needs to know about this.
[pensive music playing]
[Red] Mongki, we'll need
to expand eventually.
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[tense music playing]
Yes, but…
maybe you should get more people.
[Mongki] Okay, boss. I'll handle it.
I already have someone to talk to.
[Red] The people you recruit need to be
better than the ones you've hired before.
[Mongki, in English] Yes, boss.
[Red] This new shipment is big.
So, you need
to talk to the client first.
So, maybe you should go see him.
[both speaking indistinctly]
[tense music playing]
[squeals]
[door lock clicks]
[in English] Bring the Mayor back to me.
[music fades]
I already sent the files to the client.
I'll tell the boys, boss,
so they'll be ready.
[mysterious music playing]
Do you smell that?
It smells like perfume for women.
- But it's not Martina's.
- [sniffling]
Oh, I don't smell anything, boss.
[Mongki sniffs]
[music swells]
[smirks]
[ominous music playing]
Sir, they're here, sir!
[armed man on the device]
We're about to catch them, sir!
[in English] Let's go.
[music swells]
Hmm.
You're disgusting too, aren't you?
Hold your glass.
I'm drunk. I don't remember this.
[suspicious music playing]
[sniffs]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[groans]
[grunting]
[groaning and grunting]
[upbeat rock music playing]
Let's go.
[music fades]
- [ominous music playing]
- [groans]
[groans]
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] This is a… new costume.
[panting]
[in English] Do you like it?
[in English] Before I do something to you,
I want to see your face.
[groans]
[in English] Take them.
[music swells]
[dramatic sting]
[music fades]
[Martina, in English]
What are you doing here?
[ominous music playing]
You. Aren't you going home yet?
Well, I smelled something strange.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [sniffs]
The only strange smell is you.
[in English] You reek of alcohol.
[in English] Obviously I'm drunk, right?
Let's go.
So?
- Did you see anything?
- [inhales]
Hey. We might trend later
as scammers, huh!
Well, there's nothing!
Nothing at all.
Maybe they didn't report it
because their money was returned, right?
Friend, maybe you should focus
on Ibyang first.
- Make peace with her.
- [gentle music playing]
Oh? I'm okay now.
I just don't…
I just don't want to get attached
because it hurts when you lose someone.
Sammy is different.
Maybe you're right.
The child isn't doing anything wrong
for me to treat her that way.
[gentle music playing]
There. Thank you, Lord.
You softened my friend's heart of stone.
So, what?
What are you thinking of doing
so you two can set things right?
I want to be with you.
On Christmas, on my birthday.
So many occasions have already passed.
I have an idea.
What?
[sentimental music playing]
[in English] Dad? [gasps]
Dad, are you still awake?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] No choice.
This has to stop, Red.
[sighs]
Which one, Ma?
Ah, the plastic one there with a cover
and the handle.
[softly] This one.
Ah…
This one?
[in English] Thank you, baby girl!
Oh, later, I have a surprise for you.
[gentle music playing]
This must be Mama's surprise.
[gasps in awe]
[music fades]
[in English] Boss, what are we
going to do with them?
[in English] We have to find out
who he works for.
[in English] We have to get back
what they took from us.
[in English] Okay.
[in English] But what if he doesn't talk?
[in English] Then we will squeeze
this information from them.
[music fades]
Audrey.
Where are you taking that?
[pensive music playing]
I don't know how
you can stomach doing this.
Even my own child almost became a victim
because of what you've been doing!
[in English] This has to stop!
[in English] You're a monster!
[in English] You don't know
what you're talking about.
Give me that.
[in English] I don't know
what I'm talking about?
[in English] You're really
out of your mind!
[in English] You know that?
I've known this for a long time.
So, give it to me. Come on.
[in English] No!
Dad has to see this.
[in English] Dad?
You'll complain to him?
[tense music playing]
[in English] He knows this!
No one will defend you.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[in English] Ibyang, baby girl!
[mellow music playing]
[in English] Happy birthdays
and Merry Christmases to you, my child.
Didn't you say
so many occasions have passed?
But don't worry.
We'll catch up on all of them, okay?
Oh, go ahead. Make a wish.
[Olga chuckles]
[in English] Thank you, Mama.
Thank you also for
your gift.
I already got it.
What gift?
[Ibyang] This one.
This is the first time
I've had such a beautiful doll.
You're a meddler!
Did I tell you to take this?!
Did I tell you to touch this?!
Did I?!
[heavy breathing]
Didn't I tell you not to touch
any of my things here unless I say so?!
This is your fault, huh!
It's your fault this got broken!
You're a meddler!
[music fades]
[melodramatic music playing]
[Olga sobs, in English] Sorry.
[in English] So-Sorry, Sammy.
Sorry, sorry.
[sobbing]
[electronic blipping]
Sammy!
Child, come on. Let's have snacks!
Mommy, can I eat here in the room instead?
Huh?
No, you can't!
[in English] Mommy, please?
Sammy.
[in English] I said no.
Come down here. Come on.
[thuds]
Hey.
Are you stomping your feet?!
Don't be like that. I'll get angry.
[thudding]
Sammy!
Sam! [panicked breathing]
Sam, Sam, my child! Sam.
[panicked breathing]
Sammy! Sammy!
[unsettling music playing]
Sam, Sam!
[sobbing]
[music fades]
[melancholic music playing]
[door lock clicks]
[sighs]
Olga, the vehicle is here.
Let's go?
Um… [inhales]
They'll bring Sammy's remains
to the funeral house already.
We need to be there first.
I can't. [sobs]
I can't, Charm… Charmi.
I can't…
I can't--
[sobbing]
What they're saying is true. [sniffles]
I'm a bad mother.
[music fades]
I neglected my child.
[sobbing]
She's gone.
[melodramatic music playing]
Hey.
[sobs]
What are you saying?
That's not true.
It was an accident.
Don't believe what they're saying,
that you're a bad mother.
They don't know anything.
It was an accident,
and you didn't want that.
You loved your child so much.
Hmm?
[sobbing]
[music fades]
[in English] I'm sorry, Sammy.
[in English] Sorry.
[melancholic music playing]
[sobbing]
[in English] Sorry, Mama.
Don't call me Mama.
You're not my child!
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[in English] No.
No. No. I don't believe you.
Dad has changed.
[sniffs, in English] Okay.
[in English] Check it. [sniffs]
[in English] Now!
There.
[Red, in English] I'm sure
you know that seal, right?
[in English] It's his personal seal.
He knows this.
[in English] He is the mastermind!
[suspicious music playing]
[Dmitri, in English] Where's my ring?
Looks like it's not here.
[in English] Oh. Found it.
[Dmitri] Oh.
[Red] So, it's useless
if you complain to him.
Unless you want our family's dirt
to be made public.
Is that what you want?
[Dmitri clears throat]
[in English] What's with the look?
[in English] What's going on here?
[in English] Dad…
Are you involved in this?
- You know--
- [Dmitri] Red.
[in English] Leave us.
[music fades]
[somber music playing]
[in English] Answer me!
[tense music playing]
[in English] Are you involved
in human trafficking?
[in English] Audrey, let me explain.
- [in English] No.
- Audrey.
[thuds]
[in English] I trusted you!
[sobs] I chose you over Atoy!
I chose this family!
But you were deceiving me!
There's really no one decent
in this family!
Don't touch me!
[music swells]
[tense music playing]
[gasping]
Brother!
[Lily] Ouch.
Brother! Brother, wake up, brother!
[gasping]
Where are we?
How will we escape from here? Brother!
[gasping]
Brother!
[panting]
Ouch.
[music swells]
[Lily] Ouch.
Bro-- Brother!
Psst, hey!
Brother! [sobs]
[music swells]
[tense music playing]
[electronic blipping]
Where are we going?
To the States.
[Audrey] But, we need to go
to your Daddy Atoy first.
UP NEXT
[Janine] Mommy.
No one leaves.
[henchman 1] I'm sure, boss. It's here.
[people screaming]
[gasps and squeals]
[screaming and panicking]
- [grunts]
- [in English] No, no, no, no, no!
- [grunts and groans]
- [Lily, in English] No!
- [Lily sobs]
- [Atoy coughs]
[in English] I need you
to report to me in person.
[in English] Padua is compromised.
[Samir, in English] If you do not want
to make this simple,
I will make it very, very hard for you.
[in English] No!
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- [in English] No, please!
- [Samir grunts]
[grunts]
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
‪Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias